<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SNES on GameLibrary</title>
    <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SNES on GameLibrary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 17:03:40 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Family Computer Golf: Japan Course</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/family-computer-golf-japan-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 17:03:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/family-computer-golf-japan-course/</guid>
      <description>An update of sorts to Golf. Players get to take control of Nintendo’s mascots Mario and Luigi (in the 2 player game) and play over 18 holes of golf on courses modeled after real courses in Japan.
Players can choose to either try their skills in match play or stroke play. Match play involves two golfers trying to win the most holes. They win holes by getting the better score than their competitor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Computer Golf: Japan Course Prize Cart</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/family-computer-golf-japan-course-prize-cart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 20:48:13 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/family-computer-golf-japan-course-prize-cart/</guid>
      <description>Developed by [HAL Laboratory](/search?q=HAL%20Laboratory?&amp;max-results=12) Published by [Nintendo](/search?q=Nintendo?&amp;max-results=12) Genre: [Sports](/search?q=Sports?&amp;max-results=12) Platform: [Famicom Disk System](/search/label/%40famicom?&amp;amp;max-results=12) Release Date: 1987 YouTube: Family Computer Golf: Japan Course Prize Cart Gameplay![]() ![]() ![]() ![]() ![]() !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famimaga Disk Vol. 4: Clox</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-4-clox/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 17:51:41 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-4-clox/</guid>
      <description>Clox, or Famimaga Disk Vol. 4: Clox, is a falling blocks puzzle game that is superficially similar to Tetris or Columns. Single clock faces depicting one of four angles fall from the top and the player needs to manipulate and place them so they can form larger objects, such as simple formations like squares, diamonds and hourglass shapes to more object-intensive shapes like octagons and hexagons.
The four angles include 180 degree lines («12:30»), 90 degree lines («12:15»), 135 degree lines («~12:22») and 45 degree lines («~12:07»).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baseball</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 16:05:25 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/baseball/</guid>
      <description>Baseball is a game where the player can pitch, hit, field, and run just like in a real baseball game. The player can choose between USA and Japan modes, two different teams, and among a line-up of unique players. In the 1-player game, the player is against the computer, and the in the 2-player game, their friend is their opponent.
Developed by [Nintendo](/search?q=Nintendo?&amp;max-results=12) Published by [Nintendo](/search?q=Nintendo?&amp;max-results=12) Genre: [Sports](/search?q=Sports?&amp;max-results=12) Platform: [Famicom Disk System](/search/label/%40famicom?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akuu Senki Raijin</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/akuu-senki-raijin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 10:34:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/akuu-senki-raijin/</guid>
      <description>Akuu Senki Raijin is a vertical shooter where the player controls a mecha that transforms into a starfighter. Like Square’s earlier semi-classic Thexder, the player can opt to change between the two modes of their craft at certain points during each level. Upon touching ground as the mecha, the player is occasionally able to find other directions to continue exploring as a spaceship, presenting both vertical-scrolling and side-scrolling shoot-’em-up sections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A-Train</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/a-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 03:01:59 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/a-train/</guid>
      <description>The first game in the A-Ressha de Ikou («Let’s Take the A-Train») series, which would eventually become known overseas as A-Train. The goal of the game is to build a prosperous railroad company. Unlike the second (Railroad Empire) and third (A-Train) games in the series, the original A-Ressha de Ikou never saw an international release.
Some of the games influenced by later entries in this series include the SimCity series (and in turn the wider Sim/Sims franchise) and the Railroad Tycoon series (and in turn, the wider Sid Meier franchise).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Computer Golf: U.S. Course</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/family-computer-golf-u-s-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 02:39:29 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/family-computer-golf-u-s-course/</guid>
      <description>A companion title to the earlier Japan Course, Family Computer Golf: U.S. Course focuses on American courses. As such, gameplay is similar, with players choosing clubs and the speed at which they hit the ball. Once again, you control Mario and Luigi. Like the original, the game was compatible with the Disk Fax, so players could send their saved games and high scores to Nintendo. The gameplay influenced the later NES Open Tournament Golf, and many Mario sports games have been made since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famicom Tantei Club Part II: Ushiro ni Tatsu Shoujo: Zenpen</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famicom-tantei-club-part-ii-ushiro-ni-tatsu-shoujo-zenpen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 03:11:57 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famicom-tantei-club-part-ii-ushiro-ni-tatsu-shoujo-zenpen/</guid>
      <description>Ushiro ni Tatsu Shojo is the successor of and a prequel to Famicom Tantei Club: Kieta Kokeisha, and is the second game of the Famicom Tantei Club series. Its scenario was written by Nagihiro Asama, based on the concept by Yoshio Sakamoto.Kenji Yamamoto composed the game music. The popularity of Part I: Kieta Kokeisha prompted the release of this sequel, which employed the similar graphic-adventure gameplay. The game was re-released on the Nintendo Power cartridge rewriting service for the Super Famicom in 1998 with improved graphics and sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akumajou Dracula</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/akumajou-dracula/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 12:04:33 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/akumajou-dracula/</guid>
      <description>Every hundred years, the dark vampire known as Dracula resurrects and terrorizes the land. A vampire hunter named Simon Belmont bravely ventures into the Count’s mansion in order to defeat him. Along the way he’ll have to defeat skeletons, bats, fishmen, medusa heads and other evil creatures.
Castlevania is a side-scrolling platform action game. The player takes the role of Simon Belmont, who is able to jump and crack his whip directly in front of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adian No Tsue</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/adian-no-tsue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 16:34:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/adian-no-tsue/</guid>
      <description>Adian No Tsue is not a traditional adventure game — It is most and foremost an educational game designed to appeal to a young audience. It is also the first installment of a series of games released in Japan by SunSoft. The player takes control of a courageous knight and the game follows a traditional overhead display which somehow bears some resemblance to Nintendo’s Zelda. Each room is usually filled up with monsters and four doors lead to other surrounding rooms, different locations or just hide special items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backgammon</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/backgammon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 02:43:43 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/backgammon/</guid>
      <description>Backgammon is a straightforward backgammon simulator that allows up to two players to compete in backgammon matches. The game has a tutorial that explains how backgammon is played and offers single-player Match Play (one-off) and Tournament (multiple matches) modes. There is also the requisite two-player mode in which two human players take turns.
Developed by [Nintendo](/search?q=Nintendo?&amp;max-results=12) Published by [Nintendo](/search?q=Nintendo?&amp;max-results=12) Genre: [Board Game](/search?q=Board%20Game?&amp;max-results=12) Platform: [Famicom Disk System](/search/label/%40famicom?&amp;amp;max-results=12) Release Date: September 7, 1990 YouTube: [Backgammon Gameplay](https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ai Senshi Nicol</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/ai-senshi-nicol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 05:26:08 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/ai-senshi-nicol/</guid>
      <description>Ai Senshi Nicol is a top down, action shooter. You play as titular character Nicol, as he fights through a horde of aliens to save his abducted girlfriend. Armed with only a blaster, he must fight his way through 7 levels to be reunited with his loved one.
In order to progress, you must search each stage for three crystals. Once these are collected, you’re shuttled off to the next area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/final-fantasy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 14:35:26 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/final-fantasy/</guid>
      <description>The world is veiled in darkness. Winds don’t blow, the seas are stormy, and the earth rots. All people can hope for is that the ancient prophecy will be finally fulfilled. «When the world is veiled in darkness, four warriors will come…» And indeed, they come — the four characters you have previously chosen. Their first quest is to free a princess from the evil knight Garland, and then the real journey begins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famimaga Disk Vol. 3: All 1</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-3-all-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 01:29:39 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-3-all-1/</guid>
      <description>All One, or Famimaga Disk Vol. 3: All One, is a puzzle game in which the player controls a ladybug pushing over dice. The goal of each stage is to push all the dice onto their side so that their «one» side is facing upwards. The player is given a smaller first-person view window from the ladybug’s perspective to allow them to see the sides of each die and plan out their strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Bam</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/fire-bam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 19:04:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/fire-bam/</guid>
      <description>Bam must explore a world and «unfold» it into its full size by exploring towers and defeating boss characters inside. In addition to the starting equipment, five weapons, shields, and boots can be purchased or obtained to give the player a degree of customization.
The game sends Bam into a forest where he has to defeat all sorts of monsters. Defeated enemies drop fire elements which can be collected and used as currency inside the shops scattered around the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Commando: Akai Yousai</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/final-commando-akai-yousai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 23:01:39 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/final-commando-akai-yousai/</guid>
      <description>This earlier version of the game we known as Jackal in the west lacks some of the content that were later added to its NES counterpart, due to the fact that it was released in disk card format rather than on a ROM cartridge. Namely, the stages in the FDS versions scrolls vertically only, have different layouts and are much shorter as a result. The beach stage is not featured in the FDS version and thus, the ruins (Stage 2 in the NES version) serves as the introductory stage instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arumana no Kiseki</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/arumana-no-kiseki/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 17:12:25 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/arumana-no-kiseki/</guid>
      <description>The Arumana, a legendary red jewel, has been stolen, and the villagers have all turned to stone. Now it’s up to Kaito to retrieve the jewel and restore it to its rightful owners.
The action takes place from a side-scrolling perspective. The protagonist must advance through six stages using his wits, his weapons, and his trusty grappling hook. The grappling hook is extremely indispensable as it is used to climb upwards to out-of-reach ledges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Town Monogatari: Little Computer People</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/apple-town-monogatari-little-computer-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 14:41:09 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/apple-town-monogatari-little-computer-people/</guid>
      <description>A heavily modified port of Little Computer People, Apple Town Monogatari is an early life simulator. It stars a randomly named little girl who lives in a 3 story house with her cat. Very little interaction is featured in the game. Gameplay largely involves simply watching the girl go about their daily life. She wanders the house, occasionally doing activities like exercising, reading, brushing her teeth, feeding herself, sleeping, or even playing a game on her Famicom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bakutoushi Patton-kun</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/bakutoushi-patton-kun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 02:42:24 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/bakutoushi-patton-kun/</guid>
      <description>Bakutoushi Patton-Kun is an action game developed by Soft Pro and published for the Famicom Disk System in Japan in 1988. It is an overhead tank combat game similar in style to Atari’s Combat game. It was the first FDS title to allow for four players to play simultaneously.
In the game, players attempt to destroy one another’s tanks. If a tank is destroyed, the driver of the tank will exit the vehicle, and must try to stay alive long enough for a replacement tank to parachute down from the sky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famimaga Disk Vol. 5: Puyo Puyo</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-5-puyo-puyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 12:35:17 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-5-puyo-puyo/</guid>
      <description>Puyo Puyo is the first entry of Compile’s Puyo Puyo series. It was released on the MSX and Famicom Disk System on October 25, 1991; the FDS version was published by Tokuma Shoten as part of their «Famimaga Disk» line of games. The FDS version would later be released on a Famicom cart in 1993. Puyo Puyo would be succeeded by a much more popular arcade game of the same name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Composer</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/family-composer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 02:45:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/family-composer/</guid>
      <description>Musical Plan, the developers of Ikinari Musician also for the Famicom, developed this music creation software for the Famicom Disk System to allow users to create their own musical compositions and save them to disk, allowing them to revisit their own tracks or pass them among friends.
The game contains several dozen rhythm tracks over which the user can input an electronic approximation of keyboards, piano or organ music, much like a regular synthesizer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famimaga Disk Vol. 6: Janken Disk Jou</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-6-janken-disk-jou/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 11:22:55 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-6-janken-disk-jou/</guid>
      <description>Janken Disk Jou, or Famimaga Disk Vol. 6: Janken Disk Jou, is a puzzle game in which the protagonist (who looks uncannily like Disk-kun, the mascot of the Famicom Disk System) must brave a labyrinth of puzzles. In each room there are three variants of hand-shaped blocks between the hero and the exit: each one either making the «scissors» gesture, the «rock» gesture or the «paper» gesture. Pushing a block adjacent to another of a different type causes whichever was the inferior (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros.</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/all-night-nippon-super-mario-bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 06:18:21 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/all-night-nippon-super-mario-bros/</guid>
      <description>All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros. is an officially licensed retool of Super Mario Bros., released in 1986 for the Famicom Disk System. This version is based on the Japanese radio program All Night Nippon, and it was given out as a raffle prize on the show itself. The game was published by Fuji Television. Essentially, this game is a mishmash of levels from Super Mario Bros 1 and 2 except with the sprites of the Toads and various enemies replaced with Japanese celebrities for a humorous effect as well as item placements are different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuuun Shourin Ken</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/fuuun-shourin-ken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 20:21:02 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/fuuun-shourin-ken/</guid>
      <description>In Fuuun Shourin Ken, you control a rising martial artist who strives to defeat other great fighters. To do so, you must utilize a wide array of attacks to defeat your opponent before they knock you out first. You will compete in six different scenes against 13 different opponents. The game follows in the vein of Yie Ar Kung-Fu, and predates the original Street Fighter by only a couple of months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famimaga Disk Vol. 2: Panic Space</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-2-panic-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2015 18:45:29 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-2-panic-space/</guid>
      <description>Panic Space, or Famimaga Disk Vol. 2: Panic Space, is a puzzle game in which the goal is to reflect a laser to an exit panel in order to open the way to the next stage. The laser cannot hit any of the stage’s surrounding wall: were it to do so, it would cause the level to explode and the player to lose a life (from an initial allotment of five, though this can be increased while playing the game).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Challenge! Dogfight Spirit</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/big-challenge-dogfight-spirit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 14:50:53 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/big-challenge-dogfight-spirit/</guid>
      <description>Big Challenge! Dogfight Spirit is a vertical scrolling shoot ’em up in which the player controls a blue helicopter fighting against waves of enemy vehicles and ground turrets. Each mission takes the helicopter to a different part of the world, each with a distinctive if chromatically plain visual style.
The game’s power-ups, available by destroying smaller supply trucks driving across the screen, change the helicopter’s weapons but do not make them stronger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Challenge! Go! Go! Bowling</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/big-challenge-go-go-bowling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2013 16:46:26 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/big-challenge-go-go-bowling/</guid>
      <description>Big Challenge! Go! Go! Bowling is the fourth and final game in the diverse Big Challenge series of Jaleco Famicom Disk System games, and the very last FDS game from Jaleco themselves. Go! Go! Bowling is a straightforward simulation of ten-pin bowling, the goal of which is to knock down as many pins in as few throws as possible.
Developed by [Jaleco](/search?q=Jaleco?&amp;max-results=12) Published by [Jaleco](/search?q=Jaleco?&amp;max-results=12) Genre: [Sports](/search?q=Sports?&amp;max-results=12) Platform: [Famicom Disk System](/search/label/%40famicom?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aspic: Majaou no Noroi</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/aspic-majaou-no-noroi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 11:16:57 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/aspic-majaou-no-noroi/</guid>
      <description>Aspic is the sequel to one of Xtalsoft’s earlier games, Lizard. Aspic begins right where Lizard ends. The player obtains the Book of Truth, which is needed to break the curse on the princess. He returns to the king only to find that the princess is missing. Three days prior, a wizard appeared and informed the king that there was another way to save the princess, so the king entrusted the princess’s life to the wizard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Rock</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/fire-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 21:47:57 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/fire-rock/</guid>
      <description>Fire Rock is an action platformer developed for the Famicom Disk System by System Sacom, and published in Japan by Use in 1988. The design of the game is credited to Mark Flint. In the game, the player controls what appears to be a cave man, whose goal is to navigate a series of item filled caverns in an effort to locate the boss of the level, defeat it, and then locate the door which leads to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>19: Neunzehn</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/19-neunzehn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2010 04:17:10 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/19-neunzehn/</guid>
      <description>The heir to the throne is shared by four brave people: Darius, Simon, Thales, and Sonia. The 19 gods of Olympus left behind an omnipotent stone to the great emperor Achilles, who has ordered a search to be conducted for the stone. You take the role of one of these four in an effort to find the stone on the island before the rest, waging war with opponent armies to prevent them from finding it first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famimaga Disk Vol. 1: Hong Kong</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-1-hong-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 10:49:30 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famimaga-disk-vol-1-hong-kong/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong, or Famimaga Disk Vol. 1: Hong Kong, is a Shanghai variant in which players must remove specified tiles from a pattern. The player can select which pattern (from pyramids and hourglasses to more complex designs) from which to draw tiles as well as inputting a three letter code which offers several thousand possible combinations of the tiles within that pattern.
Rather than removing tiles in pairs on the edge of the pattern in order to access buried tiles, as is the norm in Shanghai, the player can select any tile on the board as long as it corresponds to the tile the game requests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akumajou Dracula II: Noroi no Fuuin</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/akumajou-dracula-ii-noroi-no-fuuin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2010 03:20:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/akumajou-dracula-ii-noroi-no-fuuin/</guid>
      <description>The game’s setting takes place seven years after the original Castlevania. The prologue begins when Simon visits his family’s resting ground. His back is critically injured from his last encounter with Dracula in the previous game. He suddenly feels someone’s presence, and turns to see a young woman standing within the mist. She tells him that a curse was placed upon him by Dracula during their last battle, and that he does not have long to live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Famicom Tantei Club Part II: Ushiro ni Tatsu Shoujo &amp;#8212; Kouhen</title>
      <link>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famicom-tantei-club-part-ii-ushiro-ni-tatsu-shoujo-kouhen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 03:46:48 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuushaexa.github.io/snes/famicom-tantei-club-part-ii-ushiro-ni-tatsu-shoujo-kouhen/</guid>
      <description>Ushiro ni Tatsu Shojo is the successor of and a prequel to Famicom Tantei Club: Kieta Kokeisha, and is the second game of the Famicom Tantei Club series. Its scenario was written by Nagihiro Asama, based on the concept by Yoshio Sakamoto.Kenji Yamamoto composed the game music. The popularity of Part I: Kieta Kokeisha prompted the release of this sequel, which employed the similar graphic-adventure gameplay. The game was re-released on the Nintendo Power cartridge rewriting service for the Super Famicom in 1998 with improved graphics and sound.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
